THREE IDIOTS IN KENYA
Should we eat here?
WHAT ARE THEY EATING NOW?
It might taste bitter.
AN UNEXPECTED PILE OF FRUIT APPEARS
Welcome. How many in your party?
WHERE DID IT ALL COME FROM?
THAT CAFE EARLIER
HAD A FRUIT STORE NEXT DOOR
FULL OF KENYAN FRUITS
These must be avocados.
-Yes, I think so.
-Let's try one.
Are you getting bananas?
Doesn't this look good?
How do you take it out?
-They're small, but they look good.
-They do.
Mango.
A BOWL FULL OF FRUIT
Let's buy some peanuts.
You want them in the shell
or ready to eat?
-Ready to eat.
-Okay, let's buy this one.
HE PEELS THE MANGO WITH HIS CLEAN HANDS
FULL-ON PEELING MODE
Who peels a mango like that?
OH…
Ji-won.
OH, NO
The seed.
A TOTAL MESS
It's like filleting a fish.
Just try it like this. Try it.
HE FILLETS A KENYAN MANGO
HE TASTES IT FIRST
The banana was delicious.
Hey, it's really good. Try it.
-It doesn't look that ripe.
-Just try it.
Ji-won, try it.
A BIG BITE
This doesn't taste like
any mango I've had.
What kind of mango did he have?
-It kind of tastes like petroleum.
-What?
That's crazy. Don't be ridiculous.
ACTUALLY
IT'S NOT THAT RIDICULOUS
FRUIT TRIVIA
AS MANGOES RIPEN, THEY PRODUCE COMPOUNDS
THAT SMELL LIKE PETROLEUM
KENYA'S NGOWE MANGOES
ARE ESPECIALLY KNOWN
FOR THEIR UNIQUELY STRONG SMELL
It tastes like petroleum.
-This is the freshest mango I've ever had.
-Petroleum? That's funny.
There we go.
NEXT UP, THE GIANT AVOCADO
Check out how big the avocado pit is.
-This is the avocado pit.
-What?
The avocado pit is this big.
A HIGH-YIELDING PRODUCE IN KENYA
KENYA IS THE LARGEST EXPORTER
OF AVOCADO IN AFRICA
DIRECTOR NAH TASTES THE AVOCADO FIRST
JI-WON TRIES A PEANUT
IMPRESSED
Really? What's so great about an avocado?
I'm having this with drinks tonight.
-I've never seen one this big.
-It's cheaper here.
I bet the viewers
haven't seen one this big either.
-It's good.
-It really is.
EXCLAIMS AT HOW SAVORY IT IS
Take a break, guys.
-Okay.
I'll come and get you in an hour.
VITAMIN BOOST COMPLETE
NOW RECHARGING THEIR ENERGY
Are you sleeping?
THE ELDEST IDIOT IS ON THE PHONE
It's not even 5 p.m. yet.
SURPRISED
We'll have dinner soon.
It's been a long day
since we started at 6 a.m.
You must be so tired, honey.
Get some rest.
Okay, you too.
I will.
NEXT TO THE LONG-DISTANCE COUPLE
THE YOUNGER MEMBERS ENJOY QUALITY TIME
WITH MODERN CIVILIZATION
This world-class sprinter
races against a giraffe.
Giraffes can run up to
60 kilometers per hour.
LEARNS ABOUT ANIMALS
BEFORE THE SAFARI TRIP
However, running alongside a giraffe
is only a warm-up.
Because soon, he will be facing a zebra
that runs at 55 kilometers per hour.
Let's go.
-Get ready.
-We're ready to go.
You're not going to tell us
what we're having?
-We probably won't get to eat anyway.
-You'll find out when we get there.
What could it be?
Could it be bibimbap with wild greens?
FROM A FARAWAY LAND,
HE LONGS FOR THE TASTE OF HOME
It's dinner,
so it must be something special.
I think Kenya's known for naengmyeon.
Pyongyang-style naengmyeon
with giraffe meat.
THEY ARRIVE AT THEIR DESTINATION
-I think we're here.
-We're here.
-K'osa… K'osewe?
-It's K'Osewe.
Do they sell noodles?
Feels like a traditional Korean restaurant
but Kenyan style.
Yes, you're right.
I'm so curious.
It's a traditional restaurant
that locals go to.
-It's a traditional place.
-We have to go.
-It's a local restaurant?
-Yes.
A traditional Kenyan meal.
-I'm glad we're here.
-A traditional Kenyan meal?
A FEAST FOR THE EYES AND MOUTH
K'OSEWE RANALO FOODS
VARIOUS KENYAN DISHES
A PLACE TO ENJOY LOCAL DISHES
STEEPED IN EAST AFRICAN CULTURE
A FULL KENYAN MEAL FOR THE IDIOTS
-Go on in.
-The food's laid out already.
-The food is already here.
-Have a seat.
It looks delicious.
Is this finally… What?
This is driving me crazy.
I want to try this.
-It looks good.
-Look at the stir-fried potatoes.
There's galbijjim.
EXOTIC DISHES FILL THE ENTIRE TABLE
Should I explain each dish?
-I'm switching to battle mode.
-This is a traditional Kenyan meal.
Starting from Ji-won's side.
This is a plate of chicken wings.
It's chicken.
They're chicken wings.
EVERYONE LOVES CHICKEN WINGS
And this drink is called dawa.
It's a cocktail made
with honey, ginger, and lemon.
-A cocktail?
-A cocktail sounds nice.
DAWA
TRADITIONAL COCKTAIL
-In Swahili, dawa means medicine.
-Medicine?
-It's medicine.
-It must be good for colds.
It's good for colds, coughs,
and sore throats.
This is a wet fish.
-Wet.
-It's wet.
Yes, it's wet.
This fish comes from Lake Victoria,
the largest lake in Africa.
It's a fish called tilapia.
They fried it whole
and poured tomato sauce over it.
I'm confident Ji-won will like this.
These are samosas.
SAMOSA
KENYAN RENDITION OF INDIAN FRIED DUMPLINGS
This is kachumbari.
It's a tomato salad
eaten all across Africa.
-You wanted this.
-I've been looking for this dish.
Fried rice. Chao fan.
SU-GEUN'S FAVORITE, FRIED RICE
TOMATO BEEF STIR-FRY
SAUTÉED POTATOES
This looks like galbijjim.
-It's beef.
-Guess what that is, Kyuhyun.
It's beef galbijjim.
-Did you say beef?
-Yes.
WHAT IS IT?
It's called mbuzi stew. Mbuzi means goat.
-Goat.
-It's braised goat ribs.
-That sounds good.
-But we also eat goat in Korea.
I think it'll be tender.
-I'll pass.
-You don't want it either?
I'll pass too.
BOYCOTTING THE GOAT
This one's a pass.
You can take that dish out first.
Get rid of the baekseolgi.
-What is that?
-It looks like baekseolgi.
Is it someone's first birthday?
Who's having a birthday party?
-That dish is important.
-It's baekseolgi.
The dish that looks like baekseolgi
is called ugali.
-Ugali?
-It's made with corn.
-It's made with corn?
Why don't you like goat meat?
-I haven't had goat meat.
-I haven't either.
-I'll decline the mbuzi.
-We should try it.
Even my father hasn't tried it yet.
-Your father hasn't tried any of these.
-I…
-Play rock-paper-scissors.
-Okay.
The winner should try it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Damn it.
SU-GEUN GETS TO TRY THE MBUZI
-If it's salty, eat it with rice.
-I'm so sorry,
-but it's my first time trying goat meat.
-There's a first for everything.
AFTER 50 YEARS,
HE TAKES HIS FIRST BITE OF GOAT MEAT
Why are you shaking?
How is it? Be honest.
WOW
-What's wrong?
-It must be good.
It tastes like top-quality jangjorim.
I was so surprised.
-I told you it would be good.
-Hey.
Should we get rid of it?
-No!
-He said it was delicious.
Goat can sound off-putting,
so let's call it mbuzi.
-Don't call it a goat. Call it mbuzi.
-Mbuzi.
-It's so good.
-Give it a try.
This is so delicious.
There's a reason
why people enjoy goat meat.
It's been a while,
so to remember the old days,
let's play Continue the Phrase.
Great. It's just us three.
Continue the Phrase. East, west?
-South, north.
-Yes, that's it.
-But there are only three of you.
-Yes.
-Ji-won, scoot over.
-Will a local person be joining us?
Since it's just us three,
the blame game will be intense.
This means Su-geun
will have to answer the most questions.
-Why, you ask?
-Why?
Su-geun goes first,
then Kyuhyun, and Ji-won, right?
After Su-geun answers the first question,
he has to run to the fourth seat.
HAS TO GO TO THE 4TH SEAT
Let's say Su-geun gets it right again.
-You have to come back.
-You have to return to the first seat.
-It's not that big of a deal.
-Is it over if I answer it?
-You have to get three right.
-Okay.
-We have to get two.
-Let's go.
-It sounds doable, right?
-It's not bad.
-Should we start the first round?
-Wait.
Give us the theme.
What's the theme?
The person who knows the theme best
can go to the first seat.
-If we don't know…
-The first theme is Bestsellers.
-I don't read books.
-Book titles?
Is it books?
A DEEP GROAN
-Seriously.
-They're well-known, right?
That's right. All of these books
have been number one bestsellers.
This may come as a surprise,
but I read books.
-What have you read recently?
-What?
-What book?
-I read Lee Kyeong-kyu's book.
I've also read all of Han Kang's books.
-What did she write?
-For example, The Vege?
Tarian.
Yes, I've read them all.
We can totally do this.
-What other bestsellers do you know?
-What?
What do you know?
I know if they prompt me.
I don't know them off the top of my head.
-Are you ready to run over?
-They're planning to give me a hard one.
Kill me with your best shot.
OKAY, HERE'S THE KILLER QUESTION
The Miracles of the Namiya?
The Miracles of the Namiya Boom Boom.
Hey.
Nami and Boom Boom?
DANCE GROUP FROM THE '90S
Wait, time out!
You can cuss me out
if you know the answer.
I don't know the answer.
I heard it for the first time.
You said you were good at this!
Nami? Nami and?
I don't even know what Namia is.
Which country is this book from?
-It's from Japan.
-Oh, Namiya.
-But how would we know a Japanese book?
-That's not fair.
It's a very famous bestseller.
Is Namiya a name?
The name of the store
is Namiya General Store.
-Namiya?
-Yes.
-What was the title?
-The Miracles of Namiya?
General Store.
I've never heard of that before.
What is it about?
What kind of miracle was it?
I'm sure it was something good.
Maybe they became successful.
NAMIYA GENERAL STORE,
A HOT SPOT IN SEONGSU
That was funny,
so we'll give you another chance.
ONCE AGAIN
-Here we go. Are you ready?
-No, I'm not ready.
I'm wiped out after Namiya General Store.
NAMIYA KNOCKED HIM OUT
Seriously.
-I won't even remember what I know.
-All right, Su-geun.
Human?
Being.
SILENCE
-Incorrect.
-Beings?
-Human Acts?
-You said you like the writer Han Kang.
Human Acts.
-You said Beings.
-You did.
Did I say that? Isn't that close enough?
I haven't seen these two
look so lifeless in a long time.
You can take the fish.
It's lifeless, just like us.
THE WET FISH IS OUT
-Let's switch when he tells us the theme.
-Here's the theme.
The theme is Every Brand in the World.
-If it's brand names…
-That's Kyuhyun's specialty.
-Me? Don't you know better?
-I don't know brand names.
-Don't you know a lot?
-I don't know that many brand names.
-Kyuhyun, you can do it.
-I don't know that many.
If they're brand names,
they should have name value.
That's right.
If we've never heard of the brand,
it doesn't count.
SUDDENLY SO LOGICAL
Don't give us unknown brands.
-We wouldn't do that.
-You won't, right?
-You should go second.
-Me?
Yeah, you should see
how nerve-racking it is.
Let's go! We should pump ourselves up.
-Three, two, one. Let's go!
-Let's go!
Is there a cheer in Swahili?
Is there a cheer in Kenya?
-Tuko pamoja means "We are one."
-It's too long.
-Tuko pamoja.
Let's do that. One, two, three.
-Tuko pamoja!
-Tuko paboja!
-That's not it.
-Tuko pamoja.
-All right.
-Sounds like, "Took a punch at you."
-Right.
-Took a punch!
You bastards.
-Okay, brand names.
-Tuko pamoja.
The first question.
Lulu?
-Lala.
-Incorrect!
Looloo Bidets.
-Is it bidets?
-Lulu…
Lemon?
-That's it.
-It's not Looloo Bidets?
-Lulu?
Lululala is a brand.
-Was Looloo Bidets wrong?
-Looloo Bidets is correct too.
Lululala is a thing.
-What is it?
-It's a channel.
What channel?
-It's a YouTube channel.
-Come on.
I filmed at Lululala.
I did a show with them.
-Is it a big studio?
-It is a studio.
FACT CHECK
It's a really big studio.
They're called Lululala!
-Okay, we'll give you one more chance.
-Whatever.
-The studio does exist.
-There was?
So…
-Okay, here we go.
-Okay.
ROUND 2 REMATCH
Mercedes?
-Benz.
-Correct.
The North?
-Damus.
-Incorrect!
-What?
-The North Face!
THE NORTH FACE
What in the world is North Damus?
I thought it was Nostradamus.
Then you should've said that.
What's North Damus?
What is North Damus?
Is that the name of a place?
-Seriously.
-You should've just said Nostradamus.
-The North Damus.
-Gosh. North…
What was the point
of setting an extra chair?
What are we going to do about North Damus?
THEY HAVEN'T REACHED THIS CHAIR
North Damus predicted
that we won't get to eat.
-That caught me off guard.
-Take something out.
-Let's get rid of the drink.
-Okay, take it out.
-Can I take a sip?
-I don't have a sore throat.
SLURPS
-It has alcohol in it.
-Take it away.
The ginger…
The ginger is making me shudder.
THE DAWA IS OUT
It'd be good if it were hot.
-The ginger must be strong.
-Yes.
-I can't…
-Let's try brand names again.
Please give us something easy.
-I'll give you an easy one.
-Something only an idiot would miss.
-Don't be discouraged.
-Shake it off and sit up straight.
Let's go in swinging.
-Tuko… punch at you.
-What?
Tuko punch! Just yell it out loud.
Tuko maboja.
THEY'RE TRYING TO SAY
WHAT THEY LEARNED EARLIER
-Tuko punch!
IT'S TUKO PAMOJA
Okay, here we go.
-Starting with Kyuhyun.
-Okay.
I think Kyuhyun will get this one right,
but Ji-won…
-He'll get it wrong.
-Really?
What's wrong with you?
-Get it together.
-I didn't do anything.
I was just waiting for my turn.
They just said you'd get it wrong.
Hold on. What's wrong with you?
I was just waiting for my turn.
-They said you'd get it wrong.
-Don't let them do this.
-Let them do what?
-Treat you like this.
-Don't let them.
-Come on.
Ji-won knows a lot of brand names.
I was just sitting here.
Why are you picking on me?
ROUND 3 RESUMES
-Let's start with Kyuhyun.
-Okay.
Ralph?
-Lauren.
-Correct.
Car?
-Bona.
-No!
-Cartier.
-Incorrect!
No!
-What are you doing?
-Incorrect!
-Cartier.
-What are you…
Why doesn't he know Cartier?
-What did he say?
-Carbona?
I just…
Carbs on a plate?
-Carbona?
-Are these carbs on a plate?
Is it carbonara?
That's enough. Just take something out.
Carbonara.
That's the name of a pasta, man!
-Isn't that a brand?
-No, it's not.
-It's the name of a dish.
-It's a dish.
It's like bibimbap.
-Should we take the rice out?
-We should.
Let the tomatoes go first.
THE KACHUMBARI IS OUT
-What's the theme?
-Let's do Daily Four-Syllable Words.
-I can do this.
-You're good at this.
I'll go first. I'm confident.
Was he good at this?
Just let him try. He says he's confident.
It's everyday words.
-I can tell them I use those words.
-It just has to make sense.
-You said it's daily words, right?
-Right.
FULL OF CONFIDENCE
Here we go.
Loa?
Los Angeles?
-It's loaches!
-Loaches!
Damn it.
FLABBERGASTED
Everyone here knew what it was.
Why'd you get it wrong?
His pronunciation was really good.
He said it better than an anchor would.
What's wrong with you?
I thought he was saying "Los Angeles."
I swear!
-Seriously? What's wrong with you?
-I promise.
How did you know the answer?
I'm just curious.
Why'd you say you were good at this?
-He said it was daily words.
-Why were you so confident?
This is the one theme I'm decent at.
It's okay. You did well.
-Give it one more try.
-We have to take one out.
We had too much chicken.
Let's get rid of it.
No, not the chicken.
Take this away.
-That looks so good.
-I'll buy you some later.
THE CHICKEN WINGS ARE OUT
Let's go, Ji-won. You can do it.
Even if I get it right,
I'd have to go back and forth.
Right.
So, this isn't good.
-Su-geun should go first.
-I'll go.
If I go first, we're basically giving up.
-Let's go. How hard is it?
-Ready?
This is practically a freebie.
-Daily life?
-Okay.
-Are they words from daily life?
-Yes, daily life.
-Okay, go.
-Here we go.
Noise between?
-Floors!
-Correct.
Banquet?
House.
Well, that makes sense.
It's a four-syllable word. Incorrect!
When did you say that?
-I told you before!
-When did you say four syllables?
It just had to make sense.
-I didn't hear it.
LET'S REPLAY THE VIDEO
-Are they words from daily life?
-Yes, daily life.
HE DIDN'T MENTION FOUR SYLLABLES
When did you? It just had to make sense.
-It has always been four syllables.
-For ten years.
-But you didn't say so this time.
-You didn't.
I really thought he got it right.
What did you say?
-Banquet house.
Sure, there are banquet noodles.
-It could've been banquet noodles, but…
-Is banquet house even a thing?
I'm sorry,
but is banquet house even a thing?
What's a banquet house?
Where do you eat banquet noodles?
At a banquet house.
HE PROVES HIS POINT
At weddings or old…
-Where do you eat banquet noodles?
-At a banquet house.
-Right?
-A banquet house.
That's what I'm saying.
We use that word in our daily life.
This is your final warning.
It's four syllables.
Where do you eat banquet noodles?
At a banquet house.
That's exactly our point.
ROUND 5 REMATCH
It's Daily Four-Syllable Words.
It has to be four syllables.
-Here we go.
-Hey, your eyes…
Take off your glasses.
I feel so out of it.
HE LOOKS DRAINED
Let's do this.
ROUND 5 REMATCH
Papa?
Go! Gogogo.
PAPAGO! GOGOGO
See? It's paparazzi!
-It's easy when it's not your turn.
-Paparazzi!
-Incorrect!
-It's not Papago?
-Papa?
-Gogo.
-What's that?
-Papago.
The translation…
-Papa…
-It's paparazzi.
It's easy when it's someone else's turn.
-Paparazzi.
-I've been using Papago a lot lately.
-What's Papagogo?
-Take a dish out.
I'm sorry. Kyuhyun, you go first.
Let's give them the goat.
-But this…
-Let's choose the goat.
Without rice, these potatoes
aren't a great bar snack.
-I meant to say side dish.
-It's not a bar snack.
-We don't need it.
-We know what potatoes taste like.
-Right, it's…
-It's nothing new.
-We don't have much rice.
-Okay, fine.
You can taste it before handing it over.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I always lose at times like this.
-You should've just stepped out.
-Sorry, go on.
Rock-paper-scissors. Okay.
-Potatoes?
-You dip it in here.
-This looks good.
-Let's keep it if it's good.
-Tell us if it's good.
-It's a bit dry now.
-You eat it with this sauce.
-If it's good, choose another dish.
There you go.
You can't go wrong with chili sauce.
-How is it?
-You want to take this out?
-It's so good.
-I told you.
-Let's take this out.
-We have to keep that dish.
Why do you even want to eat this?
-What will you eat it with?
-It's the staple here.
-But it's not ours.
-Still--
-We have to eat that.
-He's right.
We're here for a week.
What will they think if they watch this?
They'll see it after we leave.
This isn't our staple food.
I thought if we filmed today,
it would air tomorrow.
It's not like that.
IT'S SOMEONE ELSE'S STAPLE FOOD
UGALI IS OUT
The next theme is right up your alley.
-What is it?
-What's the theme?
ROUND 6 THEME
Let's go with Drama Titles.
-This is--
-I'm really bad at this.
-Why?
-I don't watch TV, so I don't know.
Then, go to the end.
-I'll be over here.
-Okay.
-Do you want to do a practice round?
-Better you than me.
If we do a practice round,
can you guess the title?
-I'll try.
-Whisper it in his ear.
WARM-UP
No, just say it.
-Honjeo.
-Opseoye.
-That's right.
-Is it?
But what is that?
-I don't know.
-What is that?
Is that a drama title?
-Honjeo opseoye…
-That's not a drama.
The one with IU.
-When Life Gives You Tangerines.
-I meant When Life Gives You Tangerines.
-Honjeo…
-Where did even that come from?
-I'm so sorry.
-That's enough.
-If you're going to do it like that, stop.
-I'm sorry. I was just watching it.
I watched two episodes,
but I don't know where that came from.
-Let's do it.
-I just watched it.
Pa… Pama…
-To go.
-Let's take it to go.
THEY FORGOT IT AGAIN
EQUALLY
FORGETFUL
Okay, here we go.
Starting with Kyuhyun.
The Trauma Code?
-Heroes on Call.
-Correct!
Soonpoong?
-Clinic.
-That's correct!
JI-WON'S FIRST CORRECT ANSWER
Reborn?
-Rich.
-Correct!
My Girlfriend Is?
-A Gumiho.
-Correct!
THEY MAKE IT PAST THE HALFWAY POINT
Strong Girl?
-Bong-soon.
-Correct!
-What is this?
-You jerks.
The World of?
No, wait.
-The World of?
-The World of the Time.
-Incorrect!
-What was that?
-The World of the Married.
-How could you get that wrong?
I couldn't remember.
What's The World of the Married?
-The pace… Tell him.
-You threw my pace off.
You had plenty of time.
I gave you enough time to answer.
-You did. We have nothing to say.
-He did.
ZONING OUT
Nothing's going right thanks to Ji-won.
Which of the remaining dishes
do you like best?
-What do you want?
-Everything.
-Pick one dish.
-That one.
Let's take it out.
-Okay, take it out.
-Not that one.
-I feel bad.
-The goat.
-No, not the mbuzi.
-I've tried it already.
MBUZI STEW IS OUT
We have four rounds left.
I don't think we can do drama titles.
-Ji-won doesn't watch dramas.
-I don't.
I have no interest in them.
I know Ji-won doesn't watch dramas,
but I've heard he watches movies.
-Yes, he does.
-Movies?
-He watches movies.
-He can get it right.
I'm not sure.
Let's try it. Okay, starting with Kyuhyun.
12.12?
I know this one.
-The Day.
-Correct.
-Isn't it "Moon"?
-That's the title of a drama.
Is it "The Day"?
Decision to?
-Go.
-Leave.
Incorrect!
-What was that?
-Decision to Leave.
-Leave?
-Seriously?
-Decision to Go?
-What is that?
I don't know that movie.
I hope this is the last round.
-What's the theme?
-Foreign Celebrities and Stars.
Correct! Timothy?
-Timothy?
-Chal…
-I've never heard of him.
-Incorrect!
Timo Who?
Come on, dude.
CLUELESS ABOUT HOLLYWOOD
What movie was he in?
-You don't know?
-Dune.
He was in Dune.
-June?
-Dune.
It's not "June."
TOMATO BEEF STIR-FRY AND SAMOSAS ARE OUT
We have to get it right now.
We've gotten enough laughs.
THEY GOT SO MANY LAUGHS
THAT ONLY TWO DISHES REMAIN
Let's do Daily Four-Syllable Words.
-I'm ready to roll with it.
-Let's relax a bit.
We just need to calm down
and take it easy.
-It's four syllables.
-Okay, four syllables.
-You can do this.
-We're just a bit tense.
-Four syllables.
-Let's go.
I'm getting so annoyed now.
-Don Qui?
-Xote.
Correct.
-Ana?
-Conda.
That's correct!
-Pyongyang?
-Naengmyeon.
Correct.
ALMOST AT THE HALFWAY POINT
Tira?
-Misu.
-That's correct!
-Sphi?
-Nx.
Correct!
IT'S JI-WON'S TURN
Chat G?
-Check G?
-Chat G.
Chatty?
Chat G.
PT.
JI-WON GETS IT RIGHT
Last question. Birch?
Tree.
Isn't that right? Birch tree.
Correct!
Birch tree. I got it right.
That was the answer, right?
I thought you'd get it wrong
and say something funny.
I was surprised you got it right.
-When he said "Chat G," I heard "Chug it."
-Oh, come on.
-Anyway, you guys did it.
-We did it.
-Good job.
-That was a tough one.
-Let's eat what's left.
-Can you heat it up?
-Yes, we'll heat it up for you.
-Thank you.
HE TAKES A BITE OF FRIED RICE,
HIS STAPLE FOOD
-The smell…
-It's intense.
TOO BOLD FOR HIS PALATE
I'm hungry, so it doesn't bother me.
It's good.
Kenya really suits you, Su-geun.
You usually eat like a bird.
-It's tasty.
-You've changed.
-This is a familiar taste.
-It is.
There's shrimp in here.
We went through all that just for this.
We came to Kenya for sautéed potatoes.
THE GOOD FOOD'S GONE,
AND IT'S DOWN TO A BASIC MEAL
We had a layover in Bangkok,
then flew for another ten hours.
All of that to eat sautéed potatoes.
Whenever we get together,
this kind of thing always…
-I'm grateful to be eating.
-Me too.
THEY FINISH THEIR SIMPLE DINNER
DINNER GAME RECAP
Nami… What was it?
Nami and… No, Namiya.
Was it The Secret of Namiya General Store?
-The Miracles of the Namiya General Store.
-Miracles.
I usually forget things like this.
It sounds like an animation title.
SELF-AWARE
What was Lulu again?
Lemon.
I've never heard of it before.
Have you?
NEVER HEARD OF IT
Lululemon is just…
I should look that up.
SEARCHING
They sell bags, women's clothes…
It's like a live stream shopping channel.
BAGS AND WOMEN'S CLOTHES
= LIVE STREAM SHOPPING?
Before…
I've heard of the brand,
but never checked their site.
AFTER THEIR SOMEWHAT SLOPPY RECAP
THEY ARRIVE AT THE HOTEL
SIGHS
Why did I not…
At the airport…
What?
Nothing, I was just blaming myself.
For what?
I don't know why
I didn't put it in my pocket.
-What?
-My phone.
KYUHYUN IS STILL NOT OVER HIS LOSS
I thought you let that go.
It keeps popping up in my mind.
HE TRIES TO FORGET, BUT HIS HEART ACHES
Is it your first time losing your phone?
-This is the first time.
-Oh, really?
Then it must be pretty jarring.
I lost it for the first time ever,
and it had to be in Africa, of all places.
KYUHYUN LOST HIS OTHER HALF
IN A FOREIGN LAND
I think I would've found it
if I'd lost it in Korea.
Do you think so?
I think so.
HE KEEPS FEEDING HIS POINTLESS WHAT-IFS
THE FIRST BREAKUP IS ALWAYS THE HARDEST
KYUHYUN GETS OUT OF THE SHOWER
DISTRAUGHT
HE CAN'T STOP THINKING
ABOUT HIS OTHER HALF
HE TRIES TO DISTRACT HIMSELF
TRUDGING
WHIRRING
MAY THE WIND BLOW AWAY THE PAIN
MAY YOU SLEEP SOUNDLY
AND LET THE SADNESS DRIFT AWAY
DAWN BREAKS ON THE SECOND DAY
GOLDEN RAYS SPILL OVER THE CITY
FILLING NAIROBI'S MORNING WITH ENERGY
IT'S TIME TO WAKE UP
THE IDIOTS GET READY
We have your mics…
What?
Cafe!
THE STAFF COME TO MIC THEM UP
GIVE US FOOD!
SU-GEUN OFFERS A GREETING
IN HIS OWN UNIQUE WAY
Does the hotel give us breakfast?
That's for the staff.
Shouldn't we get some too?
-I woke up early to eat--
-We're going out to eat soon.
-But we--
-Just wait a bit.
-We can't eat!
-We don't get to eat!
I meant us.
-What will we do at the restaurant?
-It's meaningless.
I'm sure they'll let us eat today.
He thinks they'll let us eat.
Why is he so optimistic?
-They didn't let us eat yesterday.
-You were pessimistic
when you lost your phone.
You were so pessimistic.
THEY START TEASING HIM AGAIN
Will they give us breakfast?
I doubt it.
AT THAT MOMENT
A STAFF MEMBER RETURNS FOR SOME REASON
Kyuhyun, your mic was switched.
-You have bags under your eyes.
-What?
-Are you wearing glasses?
-Here's your mic.
Leave that company.
Is this a backup mic?
Go somewhere nicer.
FLUTTERS
Do you want to come to my company?
-What is this?
-I can help you.
That would be nice.
COME TO ROOM 342 WITHOUT GETTING CAUGHT
AWKWARD AS IT WAS,
THE RENDEZVOUS POINT WAS PASSED ON
AND AT THAT LOCATION
SOMEONE EAGERLY AWAITS KYUHYUN
HE'S BEEN SUMMONED
Lift your heels up and down
while standing.
THEY'RE EXERCISING IN FRONT OF THE DOOR
1ST OBSTACLE: THE SHARP GUY
2ND OBSTACLE: THE CRAZY GUY
You can really feel the burn back here.
THEY UNINTENTIONALLY BLOCK THE DOORWAY
This is the best exercise, Su-geun.
VYING FOR HIS CHANCE
HE CAREFULLY GETS UP
Should I wear sunscreen?
-You have to put it on.
-I didn't.
-Did you bring it?
-Yeah, but I didn't put it on.
THE QUESTION DERAILS HIM
You'll get bitten by bugs.
-If I wear sunscreen?
-Yes, it attracts bugs.
-Wearing sunscreen?
-Yes.
JI-WON MAKES A BIZARRE CLAIM
The scent attracts bugs.
-Sunscreen does?
-Yes.
People who spray sunscreen
tend to get a lot of bug bites.
CREEPING AWAY
Really?
SCURRIES
-Don't shave while we're here.
-I didn't shave today.
HE'S TALKING TO THEM,
BUT HIS MIND IS ELSEWHERE
JI-WON FOLLOWS HIM OUT
Do you know what this is?
ENGAGES IN SMALL TALK AGAIN
-Yeah, you eat it.
-That's right.
-It's really minty.
-I almost died eating one.
It's so intense.
Can I have one? I like how it tastes.
TRIES TO SEND HIM AWAY
It's way too strong.
CHEWING FRANTICALLY
What do you mean you like how it tastes?
-It tastes good.
-Su-geun.
GOES BACK AFTER A GOOD LAUGH
Su-geun.
HE FLEES
-Su-geun.
-Yes?
Try this.
HE SLIPS OUT OF THE ROOM UNNOTICED
What is it?
Just eat it.
SUCKS ON THE MINT
-It's minty.
-Yeah, it's really refreshing.
It's so strong.
AT THAT VERY MOMENT,
KYUHYUN ENTERS THE RENDEZVOUS POINT
Come on.
-Good morning.
I had a mint, and it's so strong.
Cut it out, man.
HE PURIFIES THE AIR WITH HIS MINTY BREATH
There's a reason why I called you here.
-It must be a mission.
-You bet.
It's a secret mission, just for you.
Chostradamus'…
Prediction?
CHOSTRADAMUS' PREDICTION
-We'll be going out for breakfast soon.
-Okay.
And you will be Chostradamus.
From the moment we pass the boom gate
to the moment we take our seats
at the breakfast location,
think about what the two of them
will say or do.
And fill in this bingo board.
A 4X4 BINGO GAME
BASED ON WORDS AND ACTIONS
THE MISSION STARTS
THE SECOND THEY LEAVE THE HOTEL ENTRANCE
AND ENDS THE MOMENT THEY ARE SEATED
CLEAR THE MISSION
FOR A BOWL OF KENYAN SOUP AND RICE
-I have to write what I think they'll do?
-That's right.
Can I write what I will do?
That's a new approach.
-No, you can't do that.
-Right.
You have to predict what they'll do.
If you get three bingos,
all of you can eat.
If you only get two bingos, only…
-Only two of us can eat?
-Yes.
-Who are those two?
-Seniority comes first.
Oh, the elders go first.
That means they have an advantage.
This is a group mission.
You're Chostradamus.
MEAL WINNERS: IN ORDER OF SENIORITY
WHICH MEANS,
HE MIGHT END UP DOING THEM A FAVOR
This is actually really simple.
-Did you bring them coffee?
-Not yet.
If you haven't, don't give them any.
-You have three minutes.
-Okay.
Three minutes? That's too short. Okay.
-They'll get suspicious.
-Okay.
Saying "Cafe" still counts as "Coffee."
You have to be clear.
Is it coffee or cafe?
SQUARE 1: CAFE!
THEY SAY IT ALL THE TIME
Can I put "Whoa"?
TARGETS EXCLAMATIONS
-Sure, go ahead.
-Okay.
-But they have to say it the same way.
-Sure.
4TH SQUARE: WHOA
Filling up 16 squares isn't easy.
What else is there? Can I write fa--
NO, YOU CAN'T
LET'S KEEP OUR LANGUAGE CLEAN
-No.
-Okay.
This may be Netflix,
but that's taking it too far.
I understand.
Can I say they'll tease me
for losing my phone?
7TH SQUARE: TEASE ME FOR LOSING MY PHONE
"What did you have for breakfast?"
14TH SQUARE:
WHAT DID YOU HAVE FOR BREAKFAST?
HE GETS AN IDEA
-What's that?
-They'll talk about Tinya.
-Tinya?
-Yes.
Tinya or Tanya?
-It's Tinya.
-Okay.
-Talk about Tinya.
-If they call her Tanya, it won't count.
ONCE AGAIN, IT'S TANYA
BUT THEY HAVE TO SAY TINYA
Here's a shout-out for Su-geun.
He'll fart.
Is that a shout-out?
3 MINUTES ARE UP
I need you to confirm this.
-It's not coffee. It's cafe.
-Cafe.
"Where are we going? What are we eating?
Whoa. Talk about giraffes. Su-geun."
Tease you for losing your phone.
"Tinya. The weather is nice."
"Su-geun's phone suddenly goes off."
I don't know about that.
"I'm hungry. Ji-won. Kyuhyun.
What did you have for breakfast?"
"Hippos." They'll talk about hippos.
"He'll fart."
How many decibels will that be?
Even with all of his clothes on,
you can still feel the gas next to him.
-You can hear it clearly.
-All right.
-Here's one last new rule.
-Okay.
-You know they're sharp as knives.
-If I get caught?
-If they suspect you three times…
-Three times?
…the mission ends there,
and we'll come back to the hotel.
3 SUSPICIONS AND IT'S OVER
EX) HE'S UP TO SOMETHING, ETC.
Do you think I can memorize this?
You can take a picture.
Take a picture…
TEASE ME FOR LOSING MY PHONE
I'm so sorry!
WE'LL GIVE YOU THIS PHONE
Chostradamus, the members' breakfast
depends on your abilities.
-We're leaving in ten minutes.
-Good luck.
I'm sure they're getting suspicious.
You should go.
SCURRIES AWAY
I can't say I went for a smoke.
What should I say?
THE STRUGGLES OF A NON-SMOKER
HE HEADS BACK
WITH THE HEAVY BURDEN OF RESPONSIBILITY
-The weather is so nice.
-It is.
-It was also nice yesterday.
-Do you want some tea?
-Tea?
-There's some over there.
Just have some. I boiled some water.
Did you have coffee?
-I had coffee.
-The coffee smells good.
The cup is on top of the fridge.
Rinse it out first.
-I'm sure they'll give us good food.
-I'm sure they will.
When did they ever?
-What?
-They don't do that.
They didn't yesterday,
so they should today.
Why would they?
It's only going to get tougher from here,
so don't get your hopes up.
You're too skeptical.
It's like losing your phone.
You hoped they'd give it back,
but they didn't.
TEASE ME FOR LOSING MY PHONE
PRACTICALLY A PSYCHIC
AND IT DIDN'T STOP THERE
Su-geun.
No, that wasn't a fart. I was beatboxing.
HE'LL FART
SO TALKATIVE
Kyuhyun.
-Yes?
-Kyuhyun.
HE SAYS KYUHYUN'S NAME,
BUT IT DOESN'T COUNT AS A POINT YET
FRUSTRATED
They're doing everything now,
like calling my name.
He even farted just now.
They've already done it all.
THEY'RE NOT HELPING
Will Su-geun be able to fart again?
WORRIES ABOUT SU-GEUN'S ABILITIES
They even had coffee.
DOES IT START WHEN WE PASS THE GATE?
THEY'RE ALREADY DOING EVERYTHING
YES, AFTER YOU PASS THE GATE
TRAGEDY UNFOLDED IN 5 MINUTES
SO THEY SET OFF RIGHT AWAY
-I smacked the boom gate yesterday.
-Okay.
-It's solid.
-What is?
-The boom gate is completely solid.
-It's rock solid.
Why did you even check?
-Didn't you say it was hollow?
-Who did?
Let's film a video here later, Kyuhyun.
-By the boom gate?
-Yes.
-Why?
-For Han Moon-chul's Dashcam Review.
IT'S SWEET WHEN HE SAYS "KYUHYUN"
-You'll use this on the show?
-This is a boom gate in Kenya.
I think it's for the tanks
that sometimes come by.
THEY EXIT
Okay. Nice.
THE MISSION BEGINS
Hello.
-Shouldn't we eat there today?
-Did you sleep well?
Let's go to Ti…
We'll stop by on our way back
if we don't get to eat.
-What was her name?
-Tinya.
-That's right.
PULLS IT OFF EFFORTLESSLY
Where are you off to, Tinya?
-Are you running away from me?
-I'll skip Tinya's food today.
-Okay, we shouldn't eat it too often.
-Really?
1 SQUARE DOWN
THEY HEAD FOR THE RESTAURANT
Let's go have breakfast.
Where are we going?
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
NICE
HIS FINGERS MOVE SWIFTLY
BUT HIS FACE IS STIFF
CURRENT SCORE: 2 SQUARES
TANYA'S PLACE IS OPENING
Oh, Tinya! Good morning!
MENTIONS TINYA'S NAME TWICE
-Good morning, Tinya!
-We have to say hi.
-Is she there?
-Good morning!
IT'S TANYA, NOT TINYA
She's opening up.
What was the restaurant called?
Bones Soup?
-Bonds Garden.
-It's bones.
-A garden of bones.
-It could be something like galbitang.
-A garden of bones?
Galbitang has to have short ribs.
THEY DIDN'T GET A CHANCE TO ASK
"WHAT ARE WE EATING?"
-Don't add anything weird.
-Like what?
Like goat or…
If it's goat soup,
you should just tell us.
Galbitang is…
-If it's testicle soup…
-Right.
Galbitang should have ribs in it.
BURDENED WITH BREAKFAST,
HE DOESN'T HEAR A THING
-Kyuhyun, are you in a bad mood?
-No, I'm just…
He was upset all morning
because his new phone doesn't work.
-He can't make calls.
-He should be able to.
He kept ranting about the phone plan
and that it was a cheap one.
He also said he's going to leave the phone
at the restaurant.
Get him a separate room.
He's gotten so mean these days.
-Kyuhyun isn't like how he used to be.
-He's like the Joker now.
I have a favor to ask.
Could you please feed us breakfast?
FILES A COMPLAINT
We're going to the restaurant now.
Don't lay all the food out
and turn it into some weird game.
Just let us eat our breakfast in peace.
THEY'RE ALREADY PLAYING BINGO
You've been saying the same thing
for 20 years.
I've been drilling it into their ears.
-That drill is rusty.
-He's been saying it since 2 Days 1 Night.
He's been asking for breakfast
for 20 years.
Then he asks for lunch at noon.
He'll then say he hasn't eaten all day
and then ask for dinner.
I've heard it so many times.
PLEASE, LET'S HAVE SOME BREAKFAST
Gosh, today…
-What?
-The weather…
What about today?
-Why is it so cloudy?
-You think you'll find your phone today?
I THINK WE'LL BE ABLE
TO FIND SOME BREAKFAST
Since we're near the airport,
let's drop by and find Kyuhyun's phone.
-Which animal is the strongest?
-What?
Which one's the strongest?
The top killer is a hippo.
A hippo.
The staff breakfast…
What did you have for breakfast?
Are we going to the giraffe hotel?
There's another place we can see giraffes.
They still have to do business.
CURRENT SCORE: 6 SQUARES
BUT STILL NO BINGO
I think we'll arrive at around 9:10 a.m.
In ten minutes?
CURRENT TIME: 9 A.M.
10 MINUTES LEFT
We had to get yellow fever shots,
but we wouldn't have needed them
if we'd stayed in the city.
That lasts a lifetime.
-After one shot?
-Yes.
Even if it's been a while…
EVEN WITH ALL THE TEASING,
HE'S GLUED TO THE BINGO BOARD
-Can I go to Africa anytime?
-Yes, for life.
You can come anytime.
Ma'am, can we come…
We can ask our coordinator.
She's the expert.
Ma'am.
Can we visit Africa anytime
after that one shot?
-Yes, you can go anywhere.
-Oh, really?
Whoa, where should we go?
WHOA
STARTLED
AN UNEXPECTED WIN
Where should we go next?
Let's do an African special.
WHOA
-But we don't have a reason to come.
-Take a cruise to South Africa.
-That sounds great.
-Is there one?
-There's a cruise to South Africa?
-Look it up.
Really?
She says it goes by there. Let's go.
ONCE AGAIN, HIS LIFE IS IN HIS HANDS
The title would sound cool.
-Three Idiots on a Cruise.
-Exactly.
By the way, isn't the weather nice?
-He's in a different world.
-He is.
It's just really nice.
He lost his motivation.
Come on, he's family.
Isn't the weather nice?
It was the same yesterday.
Isn't it better than yesterday?
-No, it's all cloudy up there.
-Look behind us.
-The sunlight is so nice.
-Who travels while looking back?
You could take a look.
I can't see anything. It's blocked.
Look at all these clouds up ahead.
GLOOMY SKIES
I don't get seasick.
AND GLOOMY HEARTS
-Coffee!
-What?
-Where?
-Coffee!
Cafe!
CAFE!
Give me some cafe!
COFFEE FRENZY STRIKES
Cafe!
A ROUND OF APPLAUSE
THANKS TO THE OUTBURSTS FOR COFFEE
HE SECURES 8 SQUARES
Every time we traveled,
Kyuhyun would get a nickname.
You know, like Pierrot Cho.
Bird that cries on New Year's Day,
Cho Magpie.
-The surname Cho is so easy to tease.
-Cho is the best.
I NEED YOU TO CALL ME KYUHYUN TODAY
You know what?
We gave him so many nicknames
that he just gave up.
-Didn't he give himself nicknames?
-He made them up himself.
HE DIDN'T KNOW
HOW PRECIOUS HIS NAME WAS BACK THEN
I asked Kyuhyun if he wanted to open up
a tonkatsu place with me.
KYUHYUN
WHEN JI-WON CALLED HIS NAME
He said, "I'll make one called Cho Katsu."
HE CAME TO JI-WON AND BECAME BREAKFAST
ADDS BINGO CHO TO THE LIST OF NICKNAMES
Cho Katsu is funny.
He said, "I'll make one called Cho Katsu."
I'm so hungry.
I don't think we ate much yesterday.
Seriously? I'm still digesting the food.
Are you serious?
1ST MEAL: IN-FLIGHT MEAL ON KOREAN AIR
2ND MEAL: DINNER ON KENYA AIRWAYS
3RD MEAL: BREAKFAST ON KENYA AIRWAYS
4TH MEAL: NYAMA CHOMA FOR LUNCH
5TH MEAL: A TRADITIONAL KENYAN DINNER
THEY DID EAT A LOT
What did you eat yesterday?
I still haven't fully digested the meals
I had on the plane.
CHUCKLES
Aren't you hungry?
-No.
-You must have regular bowel movements.
2 SQUARES GOT BLOCKED
I'M FULL, CLOUDY WEATHER
We're five minutes away.
AT THIS RATE, THEY'LL STARVE TOGETHER
Are we having beef galbijjim today?
We're having gukbap, not galbijjim.
Is that all we're having?
-You'll eat it with rice.
-Rice and beef soup.
-Since it's quite hot here…
-Will you give us that baekseolgi?
PLEASE BE QUIET
PLEASE STOP TALKING
HE'S ALL ALONE IN THIS LONELY BINGO FIGHT
-We're one minute away.
-Okay.
What do you want us to do? Do a countdown?
What? No.
Fifty-eight, fifty-seven, fifty-six.
HE COUNTS DOWN,
OBLIVIOUS TO KYUHYUN'S FEELINGS
I got much slimmer.
APPLIES PHYSICAL FORCE
You have to massage your belly
so you can fart like before.
-Massages are good for digestion.
-I get massages too.
-I keep passing gas as I get it.
-Really?
They don't ask if I want a belly massage
because I fart before I get one.
Whoa, it's a huge garden.
-What is that?
-It's a wire fence.
Whoa, look at the restaurant.
I want to stay here longer.
They even serve welcome tea.
No, that's not welcome tea.
It's hand sanitizer.
-Welcome tea?
-It says welcome. Karibu.
Welcome.
That's not hand sanitizer.
HE STILL HAS 0 BINGOS
-Aren't you hungry?
-No, I'm not that hungry.
You shouldn't have told them
what the menu was.
They would've asked what we're eating.
-You already told him, so--
-He asked what we were having.
He's also not hungry.
He asked where we were going.
-He didn't ask what--
-Just get off.
Really?
He's not hungry,
and he doesn't like the weather.
Thank you. Goodness.
SU-GEUN AND JI-WON GET OFF
It's hand sanitizer, not welcome tea.
I told you it was hand sanitizer.
The belly rub that Kyuhyun gave me…
-Damn it!
-What's wrong?
WITH THE ADDITION OF THE BODILY FUNCTION
1 GAS BOMB, 1 BINGO
SU-GEUN GETS TO EAT
-He farted.
-What?
He farted.
-He did?
-Yes.
HE FINALLY GETS HIS SMILE BACK
-Su-geun, did you fart?
-Yes, because of your massage.
Massages are helpful.
CURRENT SITUATION
THEY ALL GET TO EAT
IF THEY GET 2 MORE SQUARES
CHECKS THE BINGO BOARD
-Until we sit down?
-Yes.
SIGHS IN FRUSTRATION
THE TABLE IS 20 METERS AWAY
IT'S JUST ACROSS THE YARD
HERE
THEIR TABLE IS WAY IN THE BACK
I love this season. There are no bugs.
THEY HEAD TO THE TABLE
HE LOOKS DOWNCAST
-Whoa.
-Let's go all the way to the back.
-The farthest table?
-Are we eating outside?
-Yes, we are.
-This is nice.
The palm trees make it feel like
we're in the jungle.
This place is so nice.
A RESTAURANT SURROUNDED BY
THE BEAUTY OF NATURE
Why did the palm tree grow like that?
CAN'T ENJOY IT AT ALL
I should take a selfie here.
I think the weather is nice.
THE WEATHER IS SO NICE
I'll take one for you.
HE DOUBTS HIS EARS
-I'll take it for you.
-My face is puffy.
THANKS TO SU-GEUN'S ADMIRATION
FOR THE WEATHER
2 BINGOS, JI-WON GETS TO EAT
There are some bugs here.
It's a good table to play games on.
There are a few bugs.
-Ji-won.
-Yes?
What is it?
THE GAME IS OVER IF HE SITS DOWN
DRAGS THE GAME ALONG
SINCE HE MIGHT NOT GET ANY FOOD
What?
-What?
EVERYONE'S CONFUSED
What is it?
-Nothing. Let's sit.
-Are you up to something?
1ST WARNING
What is it?
2ND WARNING
He's so mysterious sometimes.
What do you mean?
I just don't get him sometimes.
SU-GEUN AND JI-WON GET TO EAT
HERE COMES THEIR BREAKFAST
It looks exactly the same.
OXTAIL BONE BROTH AND CHUNKS OF MEAT
Look at the ribs.
A SAVORY BONE SOUP
It would be awesome with black pepper.
-Look at those amazing ribs.
-It smells so familiar.
-It's like they added a whole cow.
-It's just like galbitang.
-Why are there only two?
-There are only two.
I'm sure it's on the way.
Look at the beef.
THEY DON'T KNOW ABOUT KYUHYUN'S SACRIFICE
Why are there only two?
-What?
-Why only two?
You only ordered two.
What does that mean?
-I don't understand.
-Me neither.
You may not understand, but Kyuhyun does.
-What's going on?
-What's he saying?
We carried out
a secret mission this morning.
What utter nonsense.
The code name was Chostradamus.
-Predictions?
-Chostradamus?
Kyuhyun had to predict
what you guys would say or do
-and fill out a four-by-four bingo board.
-Okay.
Your words and actions on the bus
filled up the bingo board.
Really?
If you hit three bingos, everyone eats.
Two bingos, and the two older members eat.
One bingo, and only Su-geun eats.
Only the two older members?
Did you say the two older members?
-If we got two?
-I guess we got two bingos.
Yes, out of 16 empty squares,
you had two bingos.
Whoa! Thanks, Kyuhyun!
-You two can enjoy your meal.
-Thank you!
-Whoa, this is…
-I'll take a bite of the meat.
RUBBING SALT IN HIS WOUNDS
We've been doing this for so long
that we don't feel bad
for those who can't eat.
FOR EXAMPLE, SOMEONE LIKE HIM
You kept saying you were hungry.
What were we supposed to say?
I'm hungry.
Didn't we say that?
He said he was hungry,
but you said you were still digesting
the in-flight meal.
I think I was hungry.
You were!
Whatever I say, you say the opposite.
The weather is nice.
"No, the weather is bad."
-I'm hungry.
-Ji-won…
Kyuhyun was asking
a lot of questions today.
You should've said the opposite, Kyuhyun.
Look at this.
Doesn't this look like sand?
I personally like long-grain rice.
PERFECT COMBINATION OF RICE AND BROTH
You can pretend that we're back in Korea.
Kyuhyun, I was hungry.
This is the bingo board.
I should've said I was hungry.
If you had just said you were hungry…
-No, he had to say Su-geun's name.
-If you had called Su-geun…
-"What are we eating?" That was--
-We said that.
No, you asked where we were going.
But then he told us everything
we were going to eat.
-Why didn't you say Ji-won's name?
-You don't call each other by your names.
We've known each other for so long,
we don't even use names.
What do you call him?
I'm really sorry,
but this is better than all of us eating.
-Don't you agree?
-Look this over and reflect on it.
-Ji-won, eat your fill.
-Okay.
-Su-geun, eat up.
-Yes.
Weren't you starving today?
-I was.
-I'm still hungry.
Bingo! You just completed another line.
-What else are we having after this?
-You just completed the bingo.
BINGO COMPLETE
-What is this?
-They brought one for Kyuhyun.
-You came all this way, so have some.
-You should try it.
-He has to try it.
-Actually, Kyuhyun is an epicure.
Seriously, let me have some.
-This mini-game is for Kyuhyun.
-Okay.
-You have to speak in one voice.
-What does that mean?
-The three of you must say the same word.
-Say the same thing.
Whatever it is.
-We have to say the same thing?
-At once?
-At once.
-Yes.
THE SAMPLE BOWL ROUND
Hey, ask us anything.
-Continue the Phrase.
-Let's get it right this time.
-Just be confident.
-Okay.
Don't tell us off.
Here we go.
Häagen?
-Giraffe!
-Häagen giraffe?
-Yes.
That's a thing.
3 MINUTES AGO
-Hey, let's decide.
-What?
-We can decide it in advance.
-Decide what?
We just have to say the same word, right?
-Giraffe.
-Keep it simple.
TAPPING
Giraffe.
EYEING THE STAFF
Just say giraffe, okay?
A SECRET PLAN
-Hey, eat up.
-They planned it.
-You idiots.
-Eat.
We use our noggins too.
CLEVER STRATEGY
-I had no idea. When did you plan that?
-When?
Ji-won and I had planned it first.
But when we told Kyuhyun,
we almost got caught.
-How is it? Is it good?
-Do you like it?
I don't care
if this is oxtail or elephant tail.
It's so good! It melts in my mouth.
The cartilage is so good. It's so chewy.
You caught me off guard.
-They're not easy opponents.
-I know.
-You planned that in that short time?
-We did.
You guys are something else.
We had a great meal thanks to Kyuhyun.
-Thanks, Kyuhyun!
-Thanks, Kyuhyun.
You gave the youngest member
such a hard task.
-We had a great meal.
-I almost had it.
My heart was racing.
If you had called each other by name…
We've aged,
but we still can't read the room.
Our title is Three Idiots in Kenya,
but we're also making you eat three meals.
We should experience the culture
and see how the people live.
I'm curious.
The place we're heading to
is near our hotel.
It's called Westlands.
We're going to a shopping mall there.
THE DONGDAEMUN OF KENYA, WESTLANDS MARKET
FULL OF ALL KINDS OF CLOTHES
AND ACCESSORIES
THERE'S SO MUCH TO SEE
AT THIS LOCAL MARKET
THERE ARE 4 WHOLE FLOORS
It's the equivalent
of Dongdaemun in Korea.
It's where they sell local fashion.
You will get fully dressed
in Kenyan style.
It's a competition.
AFTER RECEIVING 10,000 SHILLINGS EACH
THEY'LL GO SHOPPING FOR 30 MINUTES
THEN THEY'LL HAVE A FASHION SHOWDOWN
WITH THEIR PURCHASES
The first and second places
have already been immersed in the culture,
so they will get a free afternoon.
You can have coffee and hang out with us.
-The person who comes in last
-Yes?
hasn't been fully immersed
in Kenyan culture.
So he'll get a chance to receive
a Kenyan skin and hair treatment.
They'll change you into a total Kenyan.
Will 30 minutes be enough?
-Yes.
-Thirty minutes.
Let's do this in 30 minutes.
TIME LIMIT IS 30 MINUTES
SHOPPING BEGINS
-Let's go.
Careful, you might bump into someone.
-There are four floors.
-Should we go straight up?
Let's go to the top and make our way down.
I'm going for a bold look
with a clear concept.
Should I go to the kids' section?
Kids' clothes sound good.
-This is super stylish once you put it on.
-Throw it on?
A FORMER IDOL WITH FASHION SENSE
Swimsuits sound good.
Should I go with swimwear?
ONLY CONCERN IS TO BE FUNNY
As long as it's funny, right?
LET'S CHECK OUT THE FASHION SENSE
OF THESE THREE VERY DIFFERENT IDIOTS
This is too expensive.
1. THE THRIFTY TYPE
THE DISCOUNT CHASER
HIS GO-TO PHRASE: TOO EXPENSIVE!
CREATES A NEW FRIENDSHIP OUT OF NOWHERE
THE MOST OUTGOING GUY IN KENYA TODAY
I SEE
2. THE EASILY PERSUADED TYPE
-Maasai.
-Shirts?
-Maasai…
-Shuka?
She'll show me something.
THE TYPE WHO JUST GOES IN
LISTENING CAREFULLY AS IF HE'S MESMERIZED
FASCINATED
YOU'RE RIGHT
WE HAVE THIS TOO
I SEE
I'LL TAKE EVERYTHING
A NEW PRODUCT APPEARS
Maasai rungu.
-Lungo?
-Yes, Maasai…
You use this to hit?
-No.
-No hit?
NOT A WEAPON
EXCITED
KYUHYUN COULDN'T LEAVE THIS SHOP
FOR 30 MINUTES
HE BOUGHT EVERYTHING
And shuka.
AND THE FINAL TYPE
What about a swimsuit?
3. JUST SU-GEUN
YEARNING TO LOOK YOUNGER
WHAT ABOUT THIS?
This is for girls.
HE'S DRIPPING WITH TESTOSTERONE
HE ENDS UP AS A MAASAI BOY,
THE EPITOME OF A KENYAN YOUNG MAN
FITS IN PERFECTLY
AFTER SHOWING OFF
THEIR DIFFERENT SHOPPING STYLES
TIME IS UP
Seriously, Su-geun?
You said you wouldn't do that.
Look who's talking! You bought it too.
Gosh, what is this?
BONUS CLIP
There's one that I made at camp.
It was called Animal Kingdom Camp.
The blue sky and clear sounds of water
The cute mountain birds sing a song
We are the animal family in the woods
We sing a song with our beautiful voices
A country with dreams and fairy tales
Animal Kingdom Camp, ta-da!
Subtitle translation by: Youla Kim